here are the stories were covering this
这里的故事都涉及这一
week in the category 5 TV newsroom under
一周在 5 类 电视新闻室 下
a government proposal to cut emissions
政府提出减排建议
new homes in suburban England will need
英格兰郊区的新房需要
to be fitted with electric car charging
配备电动汽车充电
points a migrating tagged male stork
指向迁移 标记的 雄性鹳
flipped out of contact on April 26 only
仅 在4月26日 失去 联系
to run off a 12 $2,700 phone bill a few
少付一笔 12 美元的电话费
weeks later Amazon wants to fill the gap
几周后， 亚马逊希望填补空白
left by the closure of stores like Toys
由 玩具商店 关闭 而 离开
R Us by sending out printed catalogs and
通过发送印刷目录和 R我们
a friendly reminder in case you haven't
一个友好的提醒，以防 你没有
already upgraded your web hosting to act
已升级您的网站托管以 采取行动
to use SSL effective this month google
本月谷歌使用SSL有效
is warning users that their websites
警告用户他们的网站
aren't secure these stories are coming
这些故事即将来临并不安全
right up don't go anywhere
直到 没有去任何地方
Jeff Weston jela you're building a
杰夫· 韦斯顿 jela 你建立一个
brand-new beautiful website what are you
全新的 漂亮网站你是什么
you're a terrible actor what this where
你是一个 可怕的 演员在哪里
acting comes into play you're supposed
你 应该发挥作用
to act ok I'm building a really cool
行动确定 我建立了一个非常酷
website are you building a really cool
你正在 建立一个非常酷的网站
website just because Jeff is confused
网站只因为杰夫感到困惑
doesn't mean you have to be visit cap 5
并不意味着你必须 访问 第 5章
dot TV slash DreamHost
点电视斜线 DreamHost
to sign up for unlimited web hosting for
注册无限网络托管
your website with unlimited email
您的网站无限制电子邮件
accounts MySQL databases the latest
帐户MySQL数据库最新
version of PHP WordPress and more and
PHP WordPress的版本和更多
even a free domain name registration
甚至是免费的域名 注册
it's less than six dollars per month so
它每月不到6 美元
sign up today cat five dot TV slash
今天 注册 猫5 点电视斜杠
DreamHost
DreamHost的
this is
这是
category-five TV newsroom covering the
第五类电视 新闻室报道
week's top tech stories with a slight
本周的顶级技术故事略有不同
linux bias i'm sasha Rickman and here
linux偏见我是sasha Rickman和这里
the top stories were following this week
最重要的故事是在本周之后
new homes in suburban England will need
英格兰郊区的新房需要
to be fitted with electric car charging
配备电动汽车充电
points under a government proposal to
根据政府 的提案，以点
cut emissions also wherever there's
无论哪里 都有减排量
on-street parking ministers want new
路边停车部长想要新的
street lights to come with charge points
路灯来 与充电点
details of a sales ban on new
新的销售禁令的细节
conventional gas and diesel powered cars
传统的燃气和柴油动力汽车
by 2040 are also expected to be set out
预计到2040年也将出台
the strategy comes at a time when the
该战略是在一个时候
government is facing criticism for
政府面临 批评
failing to reduce carbon emissions the
未能减少碳排放
government's target is to reduce the
政府的 目标是减少
UK's greenhouse gas emissions by at
英国的温室气体排放量为
least 80 percent of 1990 levels by the
由至少80％的1990年的水平
year 2050 the proposals announced by
2050年提出的提案
transport secretary Chris Grayling aim
交通部长 克里斯格雷林的 目标
to make it easier to recharge an
让它更容易充电
electric car Grayling's said that the
电动车Grayling的说了
proposed measures would mean having the
提出的措施将意味着具有
UK having one of the most comprehensive
英国拥有最全面的一个
support packages for zero emission
零排放支持包
vehicles in the world
世界上的 车辆
he said the prize is not just a cleaner
他说奖品不仅仅是一个清洁工
and healthier environment but a UK
英国 和 更健康的环境
economy fit for the future and the
经济适合未来和未来
chance to win a substantial slice of the
有机会赢得大量奖金
market estimated to be worth up to seven
市场估计 最多可达 7个
point six trillion pounds by 2050 Wow
到2050年点六万亿磅哇
okay okay this is absolutely incredible
好的， 这绝对是不可思议的
and it seems inconceivable to me because
这对 我 来说似乎不可思议， 因为
here we are without anything like that
在这里我们没有这样的东西
in North America but I wonder to myself
在北美，但我不知道 自己
and this is not me trying to be in any
这 不是我试图进入任何一个
way like dark or anything but how are
像黑暗或任何东西的方式，但如何
they getting the electricity like is it
他们得到的电力就像它
the electricity not being sourced in a
没有采购的电力
way that's not green do you know Rubby
不是绿色的方式你知道Rubby吗？
mm-hmm you know my knowledge of UK
mm-hmm你知道我 对英国的 了解
electrical generation is well outdated
发电已经过时了
and I know that it was very much skewed
而且我知道它非常偏斜
toward gas and coal generation renewable
天然气和煤炭发电可再生
resources were very low now I'm just
资源非常低我现在只是
checking if things have been improving
检查事情是否有所改善
and I do see that it looks like it looks
我确实看到 它 看起来像
like renewable energy is on its way up
像可再生 能源正在上升
like we're looking at almost 25 percent
就像 我们 看到的差不多25 ％
at this
在这
point now in the past the UK has as I
现在 英国和我一样
mentioned very much been skewed toward
提到的非常偏向于
gas coal with very little nuclear
煤炭很少核
renewable energy and so we're starting
可再生能源，所以我们开始了
to see that rise and that's part of you
看到那个崛起 ， 这是你的一部分
know initiatives to push for renewable
知道推动可再生能源的举措
energy sources so looking at I'm looking
能源 这样看着我 期待
at energy - UK org dot UK and renewable
能源- 英国org dot 英国和可再生能源
technology which is natural energy to
技术是自然能源
make electricity fuel sources like wind
使电力像风一样燃料
that's a big one that's something that's
这是一个很重要的东西
been really booming wind wave marine
风海洋真的很兴隆
hydro biomass and solar so now making up
水力生物质和太阳能现在正在弥补
twenty four point five percent of
24点的 百分之五
electricity generated for the UK so
为英国产生的电力如此
that's a huge rise over say ten years
比起十年来 ，这是一个巨大的增长
ago when it was closer to like five
以前它 接近 五个时
percent so I'm pleased to see that
所以我很高兴看到这一点
because it's an interesting point that
因为这是一个有趣的观点
you raise Sasha where it's kind of you
你把Sasha提升到 哪里
know where is the advantage to switching
知道转换的优势在哪里
to electrical motor vehicles if the
如果是电动汽车
electricity itself is being generated
电力本身正在产生
using dirty means right right you know
用你的肮脏手段就知道了
what this is interesting and and timely
这有趣而且及时
for me because I just bought a car and
对我来说，因为我刚买了一辆车
while I was looking for cars electric
而我正在寻找汽车电动
cars came to my mind as an option but I
我觉得汽车是我的选择
was really scared well I scared off by
真吓坏了 我吓坏了
the price point because right now
价格点因为 现在
electric cars are still way more
电动车仍然方式 更
expensive than the gas cars but then
然后 比 汽油车贵
also charging them for me wouldn't be as
我 也不会为他们收费
easy like there are some charging
容易就像有一些充电
stations in in the city we live in and
我们住在城市的车站
Barry but then charging it at home seems
巴里然后 在家里 收费 似乎
like you have to I rented installed that
就像你必须我租用安装那样
you would have to pay for us right and I
你必须 支付 我们的权利而且 我
would have to ask my landlord because of
我不得不问问我的房东因为
course it's his electricity bill and it
当然，这是他的电费和 它
seems easier in this particular case
在这种特殊情况下似乎更容易
just to buy a small little four-cylinder
只买一个小小的 四缸
car and fill up a small gas tank and not
汽车并填满一个小油箱而不是
make a huge dent in the fact that it's
它是一个巨大的凹痕
little I'd rather be electrical but I
很少我宁愿做电，但我
feel like we've got a little bit of time
觉得我们有一点时间
before it actually happens here I don't
在它实际 发生 之前， 我没有
think we're ready for it and I I can
想我们已经准备好了 和II可以
understand like
理解像
you mentioned about there are charging
你提到有收费的
stations here in our city of Barrie
我们 在巴里市的车站
Ontario and it's true but they are all
安大略省，这是真的， 但他们都是
kind of clustered together and they're
有点聚集在一起， 他们是
only near a particular shopping center
只在特定的购物中心附近
so hey if you happen to be shopping at
所以，嘿，如果你碰巧 在 被购
that shopping center or maybe you're
那个购物中心或者 你也许
lucky enough to work there and have an
幸运的是在那里工作并拥有一个
electric car it makes absolute sense but
电动车它绝对有意义但是
if you live or work on the other side of
如果你住或另一 侧 工作
town to have to drive 25 minutes to a
小镇要开25分钟到一个
charging station and then you know
充电站 ，然后 你知道
dilly-dally in the shopping center for
在 购物中心购买
however long it takes to charge your car
无论多 长时间为 您的车 充电
it just doesn't seem it doesn't seem
它似乎似乎没有
practical at all so close we're getting
实际上我们得到了如此接近
there working on it it may be what the
有它的工作可能是什么
UK initiative is is doing is making it
英国的倡议正在做着
practical maybe that's what it takes
实际可能就是它 需要 的东西
maybe it takes having them installed in
也许它需要安装它们
every house exactly Wow all right
每个房子都哇哇 好吧
migrating tagged male white stork known
迁移标记的雄性白鹳已知
to the Polish environmentalists who were
对那些曾经的波兰环保主义者
tracking him as K Jack looked out of
追踪他，就像 K杰克 看出来的那样
contact on April 26 that however did not
4月26日联系 ，但没有
stop him from making good use of the SIM
阻止他 充分 利用SIM卡
card in his GPS tracker with which the
卡在他的GPS跟踪器中
bird or somebody who found the GPS
鸟或者找到GPS的人
device and picked it apart in order to
装置和 开 拿起 它以
get at the card racked up a $2,700 phone
拿到一张 价值2700美元的手机
bill k Jack was last located at the Blue
bill k Jack最后一次出现在Blue
Nile Valley in Sudan on his way back
苏丹的尼罗河谷在回来的路上
home to Poland after successfully making
成功制作后成为波兰的家
his annual 6000 kilometer or 3700 mile
他每年 6000公里或3700英里
trip to Africa when his GPS tracker
他的GPS追踪器去非洲旅行
showed that he had stopped moving then
表明他已经停止了 ，然后 移动
when his GPS tracker showed that K Jack
当他的GPS追踪器显示K杰克
had stopped moving researchers at the
已经停止了移动研究人员
environmental group ecologic assumes
环境组生态假设
that the bird was dead they had placed
那只鸟已经死了
the tracker on him in April of last year
他 去年 四月跟踪他
in a fairly routine practice he was it
在相当常规的练习中，他就是这样
was April 26 when things got weird that
当事情变得奇怪的是4月26日
was when the scientists who were
是当时的科学家们
monitoring K Jack's tracker noticed that
监控K杰克的追踪者发现了这一点
the birds signal started moving again
鸟类信号 再次 开始移动
taking a roundabout 25 kilometer trip
乘坐环形交叉路口25公里
before it went dead then a number of
在它去世之前然后是一些
weeks later on June 7th a ecologic got
几周后，6月 7 日 生态学 得到了
the giant bill from its phone company
来自其电话公司的巨额账单
the group believes that in June someone
该组织认为，六月有人
pulled up hurt the tracker to get
拉升伤跟踪器来获得
the SIM card then used it for the
SIM卡然后将它用于
marathon call everyone everywhere spree
马拉松呼唤大家到处疯狂
running up the twenty seven hundred
跑了二十七
dollar bill echo logic said that it
美元钞票回声逻辑说它
doesn't know who made the calls and they
不知道是谁打了电话而他们
expect that they'll have to fork over
期望他们必须分叉
the money for the phone bill out of
不菲的手机话费出来 的
their own pockets so hmm now I use
他们自己的口袋所以我现在用它
pay-as-you-go so that if my SIM card or
现收现付，如果 我的 SIM卡或
my phone ever gets lost the worst that
我的手机迷失了最糟糕的一面
could happen is they could use up the
可能发生的是他们可能会用光了
remaining balance right and to think
保持平衡并 思考
that they had a calling plan on a SIM
他们 在SIM上 有一个 通话计划
card on a bird's tracker and then didn't
卡在 鸟的跟踪器上，然后没有
cancel it when the bird stopped flying
当鸟停止 飞行 时取消它
right so my question is really if my sim
对，所以我的问题是 真的，如果我的 SIM卡
card gets stolen yeah right I'm I'm
卡被盗了是的 我是我
responsible for the bail yeah you sure
负责 保释 呀你肯定
are so I think the key thing is to call
所以 我认为关键是 打电话
your service provider and cancel it
您的服务提供商并取消它
immediately let them know that hey my
马上让他们知道嘿我的
SIM card and the worst that can happen
SIM 卡和可能发生的最坏情况
is is that they cancel it and then you
是他们取消 它然后你
find your phone or whatever and then you
找到你的手机或 其他什么，然后 你
just buy another SIM card for $10 and
只需10美元即可购买另一张SIM卡
they port the number over to the new SIM
他们将号码移到新SIM卡上
card okay I have a second question and
卡还好我有第二个问题和
it's kind of an environmentalist
这是一种环保主义者
question they're putting these trackers
质疑他们正在使用 这些跟踪器
on birds so I don't know exactly how
关于鸟类， 所以我不确切知道如何
they equip them but then they just like
他们装备他们但他们 只是喜欢
once the bird stops moving or is
一旦鸟停止移动或是
presumed dead it's just like right
假定死了它就像是对的
because the tracker is dead right so are
因为跟踪器是死的所以
they just letting it just be where it
他们只是让它 就在它的位置
lays and you know what's not sure I'm
奠定了， 你知道什么是我不确定的
sure that if it was like nearby that
确定如果它就像附近那样
they would go and collect it but
他们 会去收集它但是
realistically I mean these birds are
实际上我的意思是这些鸟类
migrant Birds that are traveling great
移民鸟类旅行很棒
distances they could go down in a jungle
距离他们可以在丛林中下来
or you know who knows I don't know where
或者你知道谁知道我不 知道在哪里
they fly but you know I think that they
他们飞，但你 知道我认为他们
would go down in a very dangerous place
会在一个非常危险的地方下山
where they're not gonna go in and look
他们 不会进去 看的地方
for and who knows where it is all right
对，谁知道它是 所有 权利
and then what about predators right so
那么 掠食者 怎么样呢
you put a tracker on and a predator
你把一个跟踪器和一个捕食者
attacks the prey that you put the
攻击你放置的猎物
tracker on that's possible now they've
追踪者现在 就可以了
ingested this maybe there should be we
摄入这可能应该有我们
did
没有
you story once about making like parts
你有关于制作相似部件的故事
of hearts with like silicone or it was
与硅一样心中或者 是
something that was a non-toxic obviously
显然是无毒的东西
because it was in a human body could
因为它在人体内可以
they not come up with some sort of
他们没有 拿出 某种
tracker device that maybe would dissolve
可能会溶解的跟踪器设备
just yes it tastes like gummy bears
只是，它的味道像软糖熊
exactly I think they might be larger
我认为它们可能更大
than that I mean but it's a GPS unit
比 我的意思，但它是一个GPS单位
right with a battery that has to last a
正确的电池 必须持续一个
fairly good amount of time and be
相当多的时间和
trackable from GPS satellites so what it
可以从GPS卫星追踪到底是什么
boils down to is it's probably it's
归结为它可能是它的
probably not reclaim Abul in most cases
在大多数情况下， 可能 不会收回Abul
and in this case I think it was just oh
在这种情况下，我认为这只是哦
like facepalm that they didn't cancel
像facepalm他们没有取消
the service on that SIM card they will
他们将 在 SIM卡 上提供服务
never make that mistake again yeah
从来没有犯过那个错误是的
Amazon's move into retail has largely
亚马逊进军零售业的主要原因是
hinged around opening or acquiring
围绕开放或获取
brick-and-mortar stores but this holiday
实体店，但这个假期
season the online retailer will
本季网络零售商将
reportedly try something different
据说尝试了不同的东西
printed catalogs we're talking about a
我们正在谈论的印刷目录
massive holiday themed catalog dedicated
大规模的假日主题目录专用
entirely to toys to conveniently fill
完全以玩具方便填充
the void left behind by their recently
他们最近 留下的空白
shuttered Toys R Us chain in the United
在美国关闭Toys R Us连锁店
States
状态
Amazon's toys specific catalog will be
亚马逊的玩具特定目录将是
mailed to millions of Amazon shoppers
邮寄给数百万亚马逊购物者
homes and will also be given away for
家庭， 也 将被送去
free at Whole Foods locations while the
自由而全食地点
report compared this catalog to similar
报告将此目录与类似的目录进
Christmas season toy catalogs from Toys
玩具的圣诞季玩具目录
R Us Target and other big-box retailers
R Us Target和其他大型零售商
it did not confirm whether Amazon's
它没有证实是否是亚马逊的
planned book will be as big as those
计划的书将与那些一样大
100-plus page catalogs the report also
该报告还有 100多 页的目录
didn't clarify if or how the book will
没有澄清这本书是否或如何
include price information since the site
包括自该网站以来的价格信息
hinges so largely on dynamic pricing and
在很大程度上取决于动态定价和
prime exclusive deals this is actually a
优质独家优惠 这实际上是一个
super cool idea I think from a marketing
超级酷的想法我 认为从营销
perspective for people who perhaps
观点 的 人也许谁
haven't delved into the world of online
没有深入研究 在线 世界
shopping yet and I think those exist
购物了， 我认为那些存在
yeah I think Linden wants to know like
是的，我认为 林登想要知道
why are they stepping backwards here as
他们为什么要后退操作这里
far as the way things are done i well I
至于事情的方式完成 我 以及 我
think that this is not a step backwards
认为这是不是 一种 倒退
for them in that they're trying to get
因为 他们正 试图得到
new customers I think this is a new
新客户我认为这是一个新的
customer acquisition situation so
客户获取情况如此
they're really like capitalizing on the
他们真的很喜欢利用这个
nostalgia of the catalogues but they're
目录的 怀旧 ， 但他们是
sending them to two or they're having
发送给他们两个或他们有
them picked up at Whole Foods and
他们 在Whole Foods 和
perhaps you know grandma or grandpa or
也许你认识奶奶或爷爷或
could just be anybody who doesn't online
可能只是 任何不在线的人
shop opens the catalog and sees how easy
商店打开目录，看看有多容易
it is to get all of these things right
这是为了让所有这些事情都正确
directly to your house I think that's
直接到你家我觉得那是
one perspective now my perspective goes
现在我的观点 是一个视角
right where Linden and the foo in our
林登和 我们 的 foo
chat room are thinking about the Sears
聊天室正在考虑西尔斯
wish book and you know that was the big
愿书，你知道那是大事
thick catalogue that came out every year
每年都会出现厚厚的目录
and had everything and we would sit down
并拥有一切，我们会坐下来
as kids I'm not gonna date myself here
作为孩子，我不会在这里约会自己
Sears just went out of business so it
西尔斯刚刚倒闭了， 因此
could have been just a few years ago who
本来 只是 在几年前 谁
knows we would sit down his kids and we
知道我们会 坐下 他的孩子 和我们
flipped through and our Christmas list
翻阅了我们的圣诞节清单
was like circling the things that we
就像盘旋我们的东西一样
wanted and and our lists would be you
想要，我们的名单就是 你
know if it was handwritten it would be
知道它是否是手写的
page 273 I four and that was like what I
第273页我 四，这就像我
wanted for Christmas or for my birthday
想要圣诞节或 生日
or whatever so there's a nostalgia for
或者其他什么， 所以有一种怀旧情绪
people who grew up in that era and I
在那个时代长大的人和我
think Linden that it's not so much a
林登认为这不是 一个
step backwards as it is improving
随着它的进步而倒退
loyalty for the nostalgic look at the
忠诚度在怀旧的外观
retro gaming systems that we that we
复古的游戏系统，我们， 我们
look at here on the show look at the NES
看看这里的节目看看NES
mini and the SNES mini and these kinds
mini和 SNES mini和这些类型
of things and you think these are
事情 ， 你 认为这些是
appealing to the nostalgic people are
呼吁怀旧的人
probably not going out and getting retro
可能 不会出去复古
games because they're amazing it's
游戏因为它们太棒了
nostalgia and and there's something
怀旧和有一些东西
about when it looks like a little mini
关于什么时候它看起来像一个小迷你
Nintendo Entertainment System that
任天堂娱乐系统
really makes it brings it on home right
真的让它带回家吧
I really do wonder how they're gonna do
我真的很想知道他们会怎么做
pricing they probably won't have prices
定价他们可能没有价格
in the catalog I can't they can't
在目录中 我不能他们 不能
especially that's such an international
特别是那样的 国际化
system like the whole Amazon idea you're
系统就像整个亚马逊的想法 你
gonna have to take maybe you can scan
也许你可以扫描一下
things we'll see but take those codes
我们会看到的东西， 但采取这些代码
take them on to the website and then get
带他们去网站，然后得到
your price
您的价格
yeah I won't yeah they might have those
是的我不会，他们可能会有那些
whatever they call the QQ Qi codes you
无论他们 称QQ 齐码你
are now we're really stepping back in
现在我们真的回来了
time
时间
I don't know QR codes really you know
我不知道你知道 QR 码
looked like they had a lot of potential
看起来他们有很大的潜力
and everybody was like oh yeah let's get
每个人都 喜欢哦，是的，让我们得到
a QR code and they put it on every
一个二维码，他们把它放在每一个
product and then they just kind of
产品 ，然后他们正中下怀
fizzled and nobody uses them it just
失败了，没有人使用它们 只是
kind of seemed to die as the technology
有点似乎 死于技术
I think maybe until now maybe they'll be
我想也许到现在也许他们会
in the catalog maybe or they'll bring
在目录中可能或他们会带来
out something new and the Amazon app
新的东西和亚马逊应用程序
will be able to scan from your phone the
将能够 从 您的手机 扫描
new type of code that Amazon implements
Amazon实现的新类型代码
you watch for it I'm gonna patent that
你注意它我会申请专利
right now marking it down new QR code
现在标记新的QR码
from Amazon got it this is exciting yes
从亚马逊得到它这是令人兴奋的 是
for the past several years Google has
谷歌过去几年来一直如此
moved toward a more secure web by
迈向更安全的网络
strongly advocating that sites adopt
强烈主张 网站采用
HTTPS encryption and within the last
HTTPS加密并在最后
year they've helped users understand
一年他们帮助用户理解
that HTTP sites are not secure by
HTTP站点不安全
gradually marking a larger subset of
逐渐标记的一个更大的子集
HTTP pages as not secure effective this
HTTP页面不安全有效
month with the release of chrome 68
发布chrome 68的 月份
chrome will mark all HTTP sites as not
chrome会将所有HTTP站点标记为不
secure developers have been
安全开发 人员已经
transitioning their sites to HTTPS and
将他们的网站转换为HTTPS和
MIT and making the website the web safer
麻省理工学院 ，使网站更安全
for everyone progress last year was
去年每个人的进步都是
incredible and it's continued since then
不可思议，从那时起它一直在继续
over 68% of Chrome traffic on both
超过68％的Chrome流量
Android and Windows is now protected
Android 和Windows 现在受到保护
over a 78% of chrome traffic on both
在 铬交通 上 都有 78％
Chrome OS and Mac is now protected and
Chrome操作系统和Mac现在受到保护
81 of the top 100 sites on the web use
在网络上使用 的 前100位 的81
HTTPS by default Chrome's new interface
默认情况下，HTTPS是Chrome的新界面
will help users understand that all HTTP
将帮助用户了解所有HTTP
sites are not secure and to continue to
网站不安全，并继续
move the web towards a secure HTTPS web
将Web移向安全的HTTPS Web
by default HTTPS is an easier and easier
默认情况下， HTTPS更容易，更容易
and cheaper than ever before and it
并且它比以往任何时候都便宜
unlocks both performance improvements
解锁两项性能改进
and powerful new features that are too
和强大的新功能过于
sensitive for HTTP Wow - all that a lot
敏感的 HTTP哇 - 这一切都 很多
of viewers heard right there is HTTP
观众听到有HTTP
HTTPS HTTP HTTPS and what does it all
HTTPS HTTP HTTPS以及 它的全部功能
mean
意思
I'm wondering yeah I understand like the
我想知道是的，我明白了
S stands for secure is that right well
S代表安全是正确的
HTTP is the protocol that your computer
HTTP是您的计算机的协议
uses in order to access the Internet so
用于访问 互联网
when you look at your web browsers
当你看你的网络浏览器
address bar and it says HTTP colon slash
地址栏， 它说HTTP冒号斜杠
slash and then category five TV or
削减然后五级 电视或
whatever website you're on amazon.com or
无论你在amazon.com 或 网站上的任何网站
whatever but it starts with HTTP is the
除了它从HTTP开始，无论如何
old way or now HTTP so HTTP was the
旧的方式或现在的HTTP所以HTTP是
original protocol that allowed this
原始协议允许这样做
information HT hypertext HT Transfer
信息HT 超文本HT转移
Protocol so it allowed the transmission
协议， 所以它允许传输
of that hypertext information which are
那些超文本信息是
if you back up to the 1960s when the
如果你回到20世纪60年代的时候
internet was invented the its hypertext
互联网被发明了它的超文本
is like website content the the text the
就像网站内容的文本一样
the way that it interacts with one
它 与一个人 互动 的方式
another the way the href links connect
另一种是href链接连接的方式
to one another and so that protocol is
于彼此并且使得协议 是
used to send and receive transmit and
用于发送和 接收传输和
receive data so then it was realized
接收数据 ，然后实现
that hey this is not very safe we're
这嘿，这 不是 很安全我们
sending a lot of information over a
发送大量的信息 在
protocol that can be intercepted and ret
可以拦截 和 撤销的协议
now hypertext think about it text it is
现在超文本认为它是文本
text it is readable by anyone who sees
任何看到的人都可以阅读
it so you've heard of man-in-the-middle
所以你听说过中间人
attack m.i.t M man-in-the-middle that is
攻击mit M man-in-the-middle即是
somebody who has a server or a computer
有服务器或计算机的人
or a router or a modem or a device on
或 路由器或 调制解调器或 上 的设备
the internet or network that is
互联网或网络
listening for hypertext traffic text
收听超文本交通 文本
traffic and they can then save that log
流量，然后他们可以保存 该日志
it aggregate it and read it so if it's
它汇总并阅读它，如果是的话
confidential information now they have
现在他们有机密信息
access to that so what has happened over
访问那 就是 发生了 什么
the past couple of years and now Google
过去几年， 现在谷歌
is forcing is that all of that traffic
迫使所有的流量
needs to be encrypted so when you look
需要加密 所以当你看
at your address bar it now says HTTP for
在你的地址栏，它现在说HTTP for
hypertext Transfer Protocol secure or
超文本传输​​协议安全或
SSL and so then you are you can rest
SSL等等你就可以休息了
assured that the information that's
放心，我们的信息 是
being sent to your computer from the
被发送到你的电脑
server and
服务器和
to that server from your computer is
从您的计算机到该服务器
encrypted so it cannot be intercepted by
加密，因此无法截获
that man in the middle attack well it
那个中间人攻击得很好
can correction it can be intercepted but
可以纠正它可以截获但是
it cannot be understood it's no longer
不能理解 它不再存在
plaintext it's encrypted data flow so
明文是加密数据流 所以
Google has put their foot down they've
谷歌已经把自己的脚了，他们已经
said okay we're forcing the internet to
说没关系，我们这是在强迫 互联网
be HTTPS now if you run Chrome and you
如果你和 你一起 运行Chrome， 请立即使用HTTPS
go to a website that is not HTTPS which
去一个网站， 是不是 哪个 HTTPS
means it's secure it's gonna tell you
意味着它会安全， 它会告诉你
it's not secure so if you run a website
这不安全， 所以如果你经营 一个网站
you have to set up SSL Certificates and
你必须设置SSL证书和
you have to enforce that anyone who goes
你必须强制执行任何人
to your site it automatically puts them
到您的网站，它会自动放置它们
on HTTPS that's important and it's also
在HTTPS上，这很重要，也是
you know it's not just to stop Google's
你知道这 不仅仅是阻止 谷歌的
browser from complaining about it no
浏览器抱怨它没有
it's to protect the end users
这是为了保护最终用户
category-five TV we switch to HTTPS
五类电视我们切换到HTTPS
years ago because we want to protect the
多年前因为我们想要保护
confidentiality of our viewers our users
我们的观众对我们的用户保密
as they interact with us so that's
因为他们与我们 互动 所以这样
important to us and it should be
对我们很重要，它 应该是
important to you as well
对你也很重要
you can check out just quickly Sasha if
你可以快速查看Sasha if
I may I know you're like hey you really
我可能知道你真的很嘿
kind of took over no this is perfect
那种接手 没有，这是完美的
this has been very helpful Oh fantastic
这非常有帮助哦 太棒了
let's encrypt is a free service that
让加密是一项免费服务
allows you to set up SSL certificates on
允许您 设置 SSL证书
your website they have an amazing
你的网站 他们有一个惊人的
amazing website that you simply tell it
你 告诉它的神奇网站
a little bit about your server and it
一点关于你的服务器和它
will give you the codes that you need in
会给你 ，你在需要 的代码
order to set this up on your computer so
为了您的计算机上设置这使
it's let's encrypt dot-org you can head
让我们加密你可以加入的dot-org吧
on over there I've just brought it up on
那边我只是 把它挂在
my screen just to confirm I had it right
我的屏幕 只是为了确认 我做对了
in my mind let's encrypt org what it
在 我看来， 让我们加密org它是什么
means is that you can have secure
意味着你可以拥有安全感
hosting at no extra charge because in
托管，无需额外费用，因为在
days gone by one of the things that kept
其中一件事情已经过去了
people from setting up SSL Secure
设置SSL Secure的人
certificates and encryption is that it
证书和加密就是这样
cost money
花钱
now let's encrypt has changed all that
现在让我们加密已经改变了这一切
and it's free so check out let's encrypt
并且它是免费的，所以检查 出让我们加密
org we love free yay
org 我们爱自由yay
when it's good what's good thank you so
什么时候好， 谢谢你
much Ravi and big thanks to Roy W Nash
拉维非常感谢Roy W Nash
and our community of viewers for
和我们的观众社区
submitting stories to us this week
本周向我们提交故事
thanks for watching the category-five TV
感谢收看 五类电视
newsroom don't forget to Like and
新闻编辑室不要忘记喜欢和
subscribe for all your tech news with a
订阅所有科技 新闻
slight linux' bias and for more free
轻微的linux'偏见和 更多免费
content be sure to check out our web
内容一定要看看我们的网站
site from the category-five TV newsroom
从 类别个电视新闻中心 网站
I'm Sasha Rickman and I'm Robbie
我是 萨莎里克曼，我是 罗比
Ferguson thank you so much for being
弗格森非常感谢你的存在
here again with us this week hope you've
本周 再次 与我们在一起 希望你们
enjoyed the show please go to our
喜欢这个节目请去我们的
website category 5 TV track us down
网站类别5电视跟踪我们
track down this episode number 564 of
追踪这一集的第 564号
Technology TV and submit your comments
科技电视并提交 您的意见
give us a thumbs up if you're watching
如果你正在观看，请给我们竖起大拇指
on YouTube don't just give us a thumbs
在YouTube上不只是给我们一个大拇指
up give us a subscribe as well and we
我们也给我们订阅了
look forward to seeing you again next
期待下次 见到你
week we'll see you
一周我们会见到你
[Music]
[音乐]